A Guide to the Film collection FA466
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, Political Career, 14
  - 1969
    - Rockefeller Visit to Binghamton, Broome County, NY, 1969 November 19; Silent, Color, 15 minutes. Available on DVD. (Box 2, Dvd AV 1363, Reel III 14.1 Fg 29, Reel AV 1363)
      NAR visits proposed site of new state building, speaks at rally
    - 1969 Year-End Review, 1969 December 10; Sound, Color, 30 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.1 Ff 44, Reel AV 1101)
      NAR interviewed by Glover Delany, president of NYS Broadcasters Association, and filmed by Hal Posner.
  - 1970
    - 1970 Rockefeller Campaign Commercials, Sound, Black & white. Only available on orignal 16mm film. (Reel AV 1837)
      Compilation reel of tv spots from NAR 1970 gubernatorial campaign; 25 different commercials including issues about budget, SUNY system extension, importance of growing businesses, limiting taxes, drug policies, etc.
    - Annual Message to the Legislature, 1970 January 7; Sound, Color, 50 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.1 Fg 32, Reel III 14.1 Fg 31)
    - Bob Hope Dinner with NAR, 1970 March 20; Silent, Color, 5 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1575, Reel III 14.1 Fb 15)
      From NBC-TV.
    - 1970 Miss Universe Parade, 1970 August 8; Sound, Color, 10 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1248, Reel III 14.1 Fa 97)
      UPI News footage of NAR hosting Marisol Malaret, Miss Universe 1970, in New York City at a parade and a luncheon.
    - Hudson Highlands State Park Dedication, 1970 May; Sound, Color, 16 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 3.16, Box 1, Dvd AV 3.16, Reel III 14.1 Fg 34)
      footage from 1970 May ceremony with speeches by Governor NAR and Laurance Rockefeller
    - Election Night Coverage, 1970 November 3; Sound, Color, 5 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 1250, Box 2, Dvd AV 1250, Reel III 14.1 Fa 99)
      NBC coverage of NAR at the Roosevelt Hotel in NYC.
  - 1971-1976
    - Governor Rockefeller at Joint Session of Legislature Opening Day, 1971 January 6; Sound, Color, 30 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.1 Fe 27, Box 2, Dvd AV 1389, Reel AV 1389)
      close-up shots from speech
    - NAR Inauguration, 1971 January 1; Sound, Color, 28 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.1 Ff 30, Reel AV 1757, Box 1, Dvd AV 3.17)
      Footage from inauguration in Albany, NY
    - Governor Rockefeller Nominates Richard Nixon, 1972 August; Sound, Color, 14 minutes. Available on DVD. (Box 2, Dvd AV 1383, Reel AV 1686, Reel III 14.1 Fd 47)
      NAR nominates Nixon as presidential candidate at Republican National Convention in Miami.
    - Annual Message to the Legislature, 1973 January 3; Sound, Color, 60 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1774, Reel AV 1816)
      Footage of Governor NAR annual message to the New York State Legislature, filmed in the Assembly Chamber at the Capital Building in Albany, NY.
    - NAR Press Conference on Drugs, 1973 January 22; Sound, Color, 30 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.1 Ff 33, Reel AV 1078)
      Press conference with Governor NAR, Rev. Oberia D. Dempsey, Rev. Earl B. Moore, Glester Hinds, Dr. George W. McMurray, and Dr. Robert W. Baird.
    - George Washington Inauguration Day Ceremony, 1976 April 30; Sound, Black & white, 4 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.1 Fb 21, Reel AV 1096)
      Footage of speech by Vice President NAR at reenactment festivities.
    - The View From the Bottom, Sound, Black & white, 18 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1074, Reel III 14.1 Ff 47)
      Collection of interviews about social welfare and urban programs coordinated by NAR.
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 15
  Includes home movies and family footage, as well as some commercial and public films relating to LSR’s business and philanthropic interests.
  - Competition and Big Business, Sound, Color, 20 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 869)
    Educational film based on a study by Dr. A.D.H. Kaplan. Produced by Encyclopedia Britannica.
  - Discovering Underwater Photography, Sound, Color, 30 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 864)
    Commercial advertising film produced by Kodak, filmed in Caneel Bay
  - Dorado Beach: Pro-Am and Opening, 1958; Silent, Black & white, 9 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.6-11, Reel AV 1098)
    1958 footage showing the town and beaches at Dorado Beach. LSR is seen golfing with wife Mary and guests.
  - Fresh-laid Plans, 1950; Sound, Color, 10 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 868)
    Animated feature about business, subsidies, and the law of supply and demand. Produced by Harding College and John Sutherland Productions.
  - Flying the Boeing 707, 1950s; Silent, Black & white, 10 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 66, Reel III 14 F18)
    LSR and others on promotional flight from Seattle WA to Los Angeles CA
  - Jackson Lake Lodge Opening Ceremony, 1955 June 11; Silent, Black & white, 10 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 1611, Reel III 14.6-1, Reel III 14.6-2, Reel AV 1612)
    Opening ceremonies including ceremonial Indian dance, banquet, and guests LSR, Conrad Wirth, Kenneth Chorley, Harold & Josephine Fabian, Gene Setzer, and Secretary of the Interior Fred Seaton.
  - Laurance Rockefeller interview, 1960s; Sound, Black & white, 1 minute. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1719, Reel III 14.12-1)
    Sound bite on NYC street from LSR about being a VISTA volunteer with urban poor, from NBC.
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller home movies (2), Silent, Black & white, 7 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 57, Reel III 14 F 11)
    - Pocantico Hills NY: MFR and Laura in playpen on lawn, 1937 Summer
    - New York City, NY: MFR with Laura in carriage, in a park., 1937 Winter-1938
    - Pocantico Hills NY: MFR with Laura on lawn by pond; MFR with cousins; MFR with newborn Marion., 1939 Summer
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller home movies (4), Silent, Black & white and color, 6 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 67, Reel III 14 F 9)
    - Maine: children party, scenes of sailboats; Larry with model boat; horse show, 1950
    - Pocantico Hills: cousins dressed up as "Cowboys and Indians", 1941
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller Home movies (7), Silent, Black & white, 6 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 74, Box 1, Dvd AV 3.23, Reel III 14 F 25, Dvd 74)
    Three copies of AV 3.23 access DVD exist.
    - Pocantico Hills NY: Laura riding a pony; MFR with Laura and Marion at pool; cousins riding ponies; cousins dressed up as "Cowboys and Indians", 1941
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller Home movies (8), 1952-1956; Silent, Color, 6 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 77, Reel III 14 F27, Box 1, Dvd AV 77)
    Fisher's Island, Amagansett, Seal Harbor ME: family on sailboat; scenes of boats on the water; MFR and family practicing golf swings.
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller Wedding, 1924 August; Sound, Black & white, 5 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1925)
    Newsreel footage pertaining to the wedding of Laurance Rockefeller to Mary French, in Woodstock, Vermont.
  - Little Dix Bay Dedication II, 1964 January 18; Silent, Black & white, 3 minutes. Only available on orignial 16mm film. (Reel III 14 F22, Reel AV 71)
    dedication ceremony with LSR
  - New York Zoological Society
    - Living Earth: Birth of the Soil, 1948; Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14 F 13, Reel AV 59)
      Film from a series produced by Encyclopedia Britannica Films, Inc. for the Conservation Association.
    - Living Earth: This Vital Earth, Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14 F 14, Reel AV 60)
    - Living Earth: Arteries of Life, 1948; Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14 F 15, Reel AV 61)
    - Living Earth: Seeds of Destruction, 1948; Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14 F 16, Reel AV 62)
    - Stars in Stripes, 1949; Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14 F 17, Reel AV 63)
      Narrative "Three Little Tigers and How They Grew Up"
  - St. John's and the Dedication of the Virgin Islands National Park, 1956; Silent, Color, 9 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.6-5, Reel AV 1613, Box 1, Dvd AV 3.28)
    Ceremonies at historic and natural sites, with LSR in attendance
    Five copies of AV 3.28 access DVD exist.
  - Queen's Visit to the Virgin Islands, 1965 March 23; Silent, Nlack & white, 2 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1675)
    Footage from Queen Elizabeth visit to the Virgin Islands, accompanied by LSR, his wife, and other dignitaries. Shot by G. Hoke.
  - Why Play Leap Frog? Facts and Fun About America, Sound, Color, 10 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 865)
    Animated film about taxes, wages, and costs, produced by Harding College and John Sutherland productions.
- Winthrop Rockefeller, 16
  - Housing in the Middle East, 1960; Sound, Black & white, 12 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.7-8, Reel AV 1391, Box 1, Dvd AV 1391)
    Tour of model homes with WR in unidentified nation.
  - The Infantryman: Our Country, 1972 November 11; Sound, Color, 20 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.7-7, Reel AV 1729)
    groundbreaking ceremony for National Infantry Museum at Ft. Benning, Georgia (WR was chairman of national fundraising campaign for museum), introduction to history of US infantry.
  - On the People's Business, 1968; Sound, Black & white, 30 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1727, Reel III 14.7-6)
    film produced for Winthrop Rockefeller gubernatorial campaign in Arkansas.
  - A Time for Man, 1966; Sound, Black & white, 30 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1672, Reel 14.1 Ff 76)
  - To Do Justly, 1968; Sound, Color, 60 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.7-4, Reel AV 1737)
    Winthrop Rockefeller campaign film (1968) with Bob Hope, Jeannette Rockefeller, and JDR IV.
  - Winrock Farm: A Progress Report, 1957; Sound, Color, 700 ft./20 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.7-1, Reel AV 1730)
    Overview of Arkansas cattle breeding programs and construction of Winrock Farm, written and narrated by Walter McGraw.
  - Winrock: An Interim Report, 1957; Sound, Color, 36 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.7-2, Reel AV 1731)
    Arkansas: building and development of Winrock Farms; Santa Gertrudis cattle breeding program; obtaining water supply for farm; WR's daily schedule; building local school and clinic; Petitjean Airport; WR's personal reflections on the Arkansas Industrial Development Commission; film written and narrated by Walter McGraw
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Memorial Service, 1973 March 4; Sound, Color, 66 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel III 14.7-9, Reel AV 1736)
    footage of ceremony at Winrock Farms, AK: Monsignor O?Connor gives eulogy, Dr. Daniel Grant speaks about JDR, NAR speaks about WR
  - Self-Portrait: Winthrop Rockefeller, 1963; Color, Black & white, 30 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.7-3, Reel AV 1728)
    Interview by Harry Reasoner for CBS about WR work at Winrock Farm and his life in Arkansas (includes original commercials).
- David Rockefeller, 17
  - Chase Manhattan Bank: New Building Progress Report, 1959; Sound, Color, 9 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1064)
    publicity film produced by Chase Manhattan Bank about their new headquarters in Lower Manhattan.
  - David Rockefeller - Dresden Exhibition, 1978 October 18; Silent, Color, 1 minute. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 1604, Reel III 14.8-3)
    DR at opening of Metropolitan Museum of Art exhibition
  - David Rockefeller on Meet the Press, 1963 March 3; Sound, Black & white, 25 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 1725, Reel III 14.8-2)
    Panel discussion of President JFK's budget proposal for 1964 (DR, President of Chase Manhattan Bank)
  - David Rockefeller trip to Ivory Coast, 1971 November; Sound, Black & white, 35 minutes. Only available on 35mm film. (Reel AV 1724, Reel III 14.8-1)
    Footage from trip.
- Rockefeller Foundation, 18
  - Adventure in Sardinia, 1950; Sound, Black & white, 20 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel II 50.6 Fd 4, Box 1, Dvd AV 126, Reel AV 126)
    The second half of a film about the ERLAAS project in Sardinia (The first half is "The Sardinian Project"). Describes the land and people of Sardinia before the malaria eradication program - difficulties of life in villages, land defoliated, rampant disease, and so on. Introduces the ERLAAS staff, under the direction of Dr. John Loyan, and their efforts to combat the disease using DDT spray over 10,000 square miles. Produced by British Pathe Production for the Economic Cooperation Administration.
  - Botanical Expedition to the Heart of the Aegilops, 1963; Sound, Color, 9 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 125, Reel II 50.6 Fd 3)
    The search for perfected strains of wheat in Greece, Lebanon, Turkey, and Egypt. Footage from Ankar University laboratories with agricultural research.
  - Buscando Una Agricultura Mejor, 1958; Sound, Color, 28 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 28, Reel II 50.6 Fe 53)
    Film of the Cotaxtla Experimental Station in Mexico, researching food sources such as bananas, mangoes, and pineapples. Irrigation, weeding, cross-breeding, lab work, and inspection of variant plant strands. Construction of farm buildings and specialized machinery. Farmers from across Mexico coming to Cotaxtla for training and modernization.
  - La Ciencia Agricola Impulsa Al Noroeste, 1960s; Sound, Color, 22 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 29, Reel II 50.6 Fe 56)
    film about agricultural sciences in Mexico; new research and technologies encouraging cross-breeding, pesticides, irrigation, etc.
  - Comentarios Sobre Asistencia Technica Cooperativa Por Su Excelencia Don Julian Rodriguez Adame, Secretario de Agricultura Y Ganadera, Republica de Mexico, 1961; Sound, Black & white, 6 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 121, Reel II 50.6 Fb 15)
    Unedited trims from 1961 film of His Excellency Don Julian Rodrigues-Adame, Secretary of Agriculture and Livestock, Republic of Mexico, commenting on cooperative RF/Mexican farm research projects. Part of the film Harvest.
  - Composers & Performers Workshop, 1965; Silent, Black & white, 9 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 113, Reel II 50.6 Fb 2)
    conference at the North Texas State University in Dallas, Texas (funded by an RF grant).
  - La Cria de Pollitos, 1961; Sound, Color, 14 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 129, Reel II 50.6 Fd 7)
    film of scientific methods in Mexico for breeding chickens. Shows incubators, cross-breeding, sanitation methods, warming environments, etc.
  - Dorothy Gordon Youth Forum: The Well-Being of Mankind, Part I, 1963 March 31; Sound, Color, 31 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 46, Reel II 50.6 Fe 60)
    Interview with J.G. Harrar, Ralph Bunche, and several international RF Fellows in connection with the RF 50th anniversary, and the publication of "The Well-Being of Mankind". Questions: is the RF work aiding mankind? Is the training applicable to the real world? What are the most acute needs in certain countries? What is the United Nations doing to help poverty-sticken populations?
  - Dorothy Gordon Youth Forum: The Well-Being of Mankind, Part II, 1963 April 7; Sound, Color, 31 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 48, Reel II 50.6 Fe 62)
    Continuation of interview with J.G Harrar, Ralph Bunche, and several international RF Fellows in connection with the RF 50th anniversary, and the publication of "The Well-Being of Mankind". Questions: What is the role of the private foundation? How do you feel about the recently-inaugurated Peace Corps? Are the RF and other organizations making real change in the US?
  - Dr. Eisenhower Vista Cotaxtla, 1960; Silent, Black & white, 8 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fb 13, Reel AV 119)
    Dr. Milton Eisenhower visits with RF staff at the Cotaxtla labs
  - An Eight Months Experiment, 1933; Silent, Black & white, 29 minutes (with time code). Available on DVD. (Box 1, Dvd AV 115, Reel II 50.6 Fb 7, 8, 9, Reel AV 115)
    Chinese and English subtitles.
    Three part film about the Peking Union Medical College and its efforts to improve the treatment and conditions for mentally ill patients. Features the Bureau of Public Welfare as well as the PUMC, with footage of clinics, patient activities, procedures, therapy, etc (some graphic imagery).
  - Los Expertos Contestan (The Experts Answer), 1963; Sound, Color, 60 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fe 52, Reel AV 44)
    Interview with J.G. Harrar, produced by the U.S. Information Service
  - Feeding the Billions: Tomorrow's World, 1968; Sound, Color, 60 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fg 1, Reel AV 148)
    Film about food sources for the future: population developments and how agriculture and the environment will have to adapt to keep up with the need. IRRI work and other scientific solutions.
  - Forrage Ensilado, 1960; Sound, Color, 15 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fd 10, Reel AV 132)
    Mexican efforts to improve dairy practices: forage crops, enriched milk via experimental strains of grass, and restoring depleted lands.
  - Harvest, 1961; Sound, Color, 33 minutes. Available on DVD. (Box 1, Dvd AV 861, Dvd AV 107, Reel AV 861)
    Film showing agricultural experiments in Mexico, Chile, Argentina, and Columbia, but focuses on production and research in Mexico. Footage of E.J. Welhausen discussing RF experimental work, lab experiments, cross-breeding, etc. The RAC also has the unedited original footage from this production.
  - La Herencia Del Ganadero, 1960; Sound, Color, 14 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fd 9, Reel AV 131)
    film about cattle farming in La Campana, Mexico. Randers driving cattle, usage of improved grains and grasses, experimental pesticides, identification of grass seeds, and proper water systems.
  - Horizontes: La Revolucion Verde (The Green Revolution), Sound, Color, 14 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel II 50.6 Fd 5, Fd 6, Reel AV 134, Box 1, Dvd AV 134)
    The agricultural revolution in Mexico, Pakistan, India, Canada, Australia, and others. Shows Norman Borlaug receiving the Nobel Peace Prize for his related work, as well as field footage of Borlaug with farmers. Existing farming methods combined with modern techniques of fertilization, irrigation, crop rotation, and breeding methods.
  - International Rice Research Institute, 1965; Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fb 3, Reel AV 114)
    film about new IRRI headquarters in the Philippines, with dedication ceremonies with guests JDR 3rd, J.G. Harrar, and Robert Chandler. Discussion of their concerns and efforts, including traditional rice farming, scientific methods, fertilization, laboratory work, etc.
  - International Rice Research Institute: Harvest of Energy, Sound, Color, 25 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 144, Reel II 50.6 Fe 1)
  - Let's Visit the College of Veterinary Medicine, Kasetsart University, Bangkok, Thailand, 1962; Sound, Black & white, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 118, Reel II 50.6 Fb 11, Fb 12)
    life at the veterinary school; laboratory, patients, operations on dogs and cattle, all with support from the Rockefeller Foundation. Features Dr. Luang Chai Asvaran, director of program, plus footage from university commencement attended by the King and Queen of Thailand.
  - A Man, His Ranch, and Merkeron (Una Ganadero, Su Rancho, U Zacate Merkeron), 1965; Sound, Black & white, 12 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 116, Reel II 50.6 Fb 10)
    film about agriculture in Mexico; Mexican dairy farmers at work, scientific approaches towards improving production, experimental lab work. Focus on fertilizing healthier grass in Merkeron.
  - "Of Men and Ideas", Interview with J.G. Harrar, 1963 April 4; Sound, Black & white, 60 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 149, Box 1, Dvd AV 149, Reel II 50.6 Fg 2, 3, 4)
    Episode titled "Role of Foundations in Today's World". Host Richard Heffner, Channel WNDT manager, interviews J.G. Harrar, the president of the Rockefeller Foundation. Some questions: Is the phenomenon of giving strictly American? Do people within wealthy foundations play the role of God? What role do you think foundations will play in the future? What is an appropriate relationship between foundation and government policy?
  - Mexican Agricultural Program, 1950; Sound, Color, 15 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 860, Box 1, Dvd AV 860, Reel II 50.6 Fd 12)
    The Mexican Agricultural Program (MAP) is also sometimes referred to as "Mexican Agriculture" or "Experiment to Revitalize Mexican Agriculture".
    "An experiment in International Cooperation between the government of Mexico and the Rockefeller Foundation": film introducing partnership between the Mexican government and the Rockefeller Foundation, and the focus of their work. Scenes of women making tortillas, Mexican corn varieties, cross-breeding plants, fight against plant disease, and experimentation with fertilizers.
  - One Tenth of Our Nation, 1940; Sound, Black & white, 25 minutes. Available on DVD. (Reel AV 31, Reel II 50.6 Fe 56, Box 1, Dvd AV 311)
    Film produced in 1940 by the General Education Board which shows the limitations of education for the black population in the American South. History and current conditions of African Americans, from slavery and farming to special high school and college programs. Contrasting shots of impoverished villages and poor farms, with educated children learning job skills and modern training. Footage from George Washington Carver College.
  - "Open Mind" with Dr. John H. Knowles, Sound, Color, 28 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 872, Reel IV 2A 2.7 Fe 1)
    Episode #0215 with Richard D. Heffner (Rutgers University) and Dr. John H. Knowles (RF).
  - Peking and Its Environs, c. 1920; Silent, Black & white, 31 minutes (with time code). Available on DVD. (Box 1, Dvd AV 122, Reel AV 2.10, Reel II 50.6 Fb 4, Fb 5, Fb 6, Reel AV 122)
    Produced by the Peking Union Medical College, the film shows the activities of the city and its people, historic sites, local natural features, and the campus of PUMC.
    Three copies of access DVDs.
  - Population Ecology, 1963; Sound, Color, 20 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel III 14.4-12, Reel AV 1705)
    Film made by Encyclopedia Britannica about the agricultural revolution and meeting the needs of a growing population. Uses lab tests with fruit flies and mice to discuss ecosystem restraints and natural population controls.
  - Programa de Adiestramiento Agro-Pecuario Popular, Sound, Black & white, 15 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel AV 747)
    Training film about improving animal use on farms, presented by the Council of Rural Life.
  - Promises and Progress, 1967; Sound, Color, 11 minutes. Only available on original 16mm film. (Reel II 50.6 Fd 8, Reel AV 130)
    Training film from the Mexican Ministry of Agriculture. Shows the interaction of RF officers with farmers and at stations. Experiments with potato production, disease-resistant seeds and cross-breeding, and preparation of soil.